

# ABDUSELAM MOHAMMED | DATA SCIENTIST | PYTHON DEVELOPER

■ abduselamm555@gmail.com

+251925962096

Adama

## 

Python back-end

Python | Django(Programming language)

Linux | Competitive Programming

Data science|Data Analysis| web development

Leadership

## Reference

Dr.Biruk Yirga - "ASTU"

CSE Department Head and Assistant Professor in ASTU birukyirga73@gmail.com +251949807337

Professor Wazih Ahmad - "ASTU"

Assistant Professor at ASTU wazihmohammed786@gmail.com +251 97 453 9475

# Languages

English •Full Professional Proficiency

Arabic •Fluent Proficiency

#### Personal Details

GitHub: https://github.com/abduselamm

# Objective

Motivated Python programmer trained with 4+ years of experience. And highly effective at Data analysis and in data science using python and task automation. Exceptional interpersonal Communication, and multitasking abilities. Prepared to deliver first-rate results to clients

# Experience

O ICPC 28-12-2020
AACPC contests - 29-12-

I have participated as a contestant for ACPC 2021. 2020

Wollo University tulana University and Microsoft4africa app

factory academy 13-06-2020

İnternship program - 10-08-

I have gained hands-on development system 2020 specially for web development and optimization systems and team work In addition data science skills and leadership skills.

**ASTU** 2020 - 2021

TEAM LEADER FOR GRADUATING PROJECTS | CSE ASTU Managing and helping my team with the project, dividing and giving tasks to each member, and developing the backend of the project implementation

## ASTU space science

2020 - 2021

Space Science and Technology Club member |ASTU work collaboratively in a this club which was aimed for developers who have interest in Aerospace,satellite and in AI and Robotics based projects and new inovation techologies .

Adama Industrial park development corporation 2019 - 2020

ADAMA IPDC Land Information and geospatial data

Management system

Work as back-end developer and team leader

### Education

Adama science and technology University

Computer science and engineering

Graduated

2021